[
    {
        "question": "Which is the origin city of Targaryen dynysty?",
        "options": [
            "essos",
            "pentos",
            "Valyria",
            "oldtown"
        ],
        "correct": "Valyria",
        "score": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "Which was the language used by KHalisi?",
        "options": [
            "Dothraki",
            "bravosi",
            "northern",
            "High valyrian"
        ],
        "correct": "dothraki",
        "score": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "which was the seat of targaryen empire after the doom?",
        "options": [
            "hightower",
            "red keep",
            "dragonstone",
            "the vale"
        ],
        "correct": "dragonstone",
        "score": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "who were responsible for the knight king?",
        "options": [
            "starks",
            "children of the forest",
            "faith of the seven",
            "bravosi"
        ],
        "correct": "children of the forest",
        "score": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "who saved the targaryens from the doom?",
        "options": [
            "daenys",
            "jon snow",
            "drogon",
            "rhegar"
        ],
        "correct": "daenys",
        "score": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "what is the name of aegon's dragon?",
        "options": [
            "drogon",
            "vhagar",
            "balerion",
            "vermithor"
        ],
        "correct": "balerion",
        "score": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "what was the real name of the mad king?",
        "options": [
            "aryes",
            "viserys",
            "geoffrey",
            "aemond"
        ],
        "correct": "aryes",
        "score": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "what were the bastards called in the north?",
        "options": [
            "wildlings",
            "snow",
            "fringes",
            "birds"
        ],
        "correct": "snow",
        "score": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "who created house lannister?",
        "options": [
            "cersie",
            "jaimie",
            "lann",
            "robert"
        ],
        "correct": "lann",
        "score": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "who was the the most beautifull dragon that ever lived?",
        "options": [
            "seasmoke",
            "syrax",
            "mylyes",
            "sunfyre"
        ],
        "correct": "sunfyre",
        "score": 5
    }
]